Hello! I'm Shachi!
There are four of us today.
It's lunchtime.
Are you hungry?
Yes, I am!
I'm starving.
Today we are supporting a small udon shop.
Small udon noodles
Listen, everyone!
Noodles made with care
Dashi (soup stock)
The most important thing is
It's always just right!
This size
Don't you want some?
Plus One for you
Plus one small udon
Would you like some?
Sugakiya
Where are you all today?
Sugakiya!
Sugaki
Sugaki-ya!
What a little udon noodle!
A new product was released on September 4!
Congratulations!
Little Udon Noodles
A new product has been released!
Looks so delicious!Looks so good!
What flavor?
Ginger sauce!
Delicious.
Why don't you let it cool down now?
I like it cold.
It's getting cold.
Let's eat this this time.
Yay.
I'm going to play word wolf.
Suddenly I've gone from some kind of skill to hunchback.
Hunchback of the Word Wolf, please.
Yes, I'll take care of it.
I'll take care of it.
I'll explain the rules.
Word Wolf?
I'll explain the rules of Word Wolves.
I'll explain Word Wolf.
Each of you has a subject.
One for each of you, and it'll be right here on the screen.
Okay.
And the subject is simply three words.
For example, a cup or chopsticks.
I don't know what I'm going to get.
I don't know what I'm going to get, but I'm going to discuss it with everyone.
Everyone discusses about the theme that was given to them
But there was one person who was given a different theme.
Yes.
But I don't know if I'm the only one.
I don't know if I'm different or not, but in the discussion I'm in a state of not knowing, but in our discussions.
I might be different, this girl might be different, and so on.
The game will be a game of discernment.
If a decimalist is able to discern the difference, he/she loses.
That's right.
If you guess right, you lose.
That's why the decimalist has to guess
I wonder which theme the decimals are going for.
and match it to that theme.
That's perfect.
Yeah, that's perfect.
That's also possible.
Yuyuki, I felt it in my head for about a minute.
I got it.
Can you do it?
While we're talking.
Okay, I got it.
I'll stop talking.
Sometimes it's a good game.
That's right.
Some of the best games I've ever seen.
Want the three of us to practice while Hal does his thing?
Oh, that's good. Like this.
It's a little something like this.
Okay, let's start with the three of us.
I'll take a look at the subject.
Thank you, Hal.
You got a boyfriend?
I think he's on his way.
Yes, I've got him. Yes, I remember.
Okay, main.
I'll tell you.
I have the impression
I have the impression that you like Honoka.
Ehhhh...
Huh?
I don't.
By the way, I never eat it.
I don't eat it.
Me neither.
And I won't eat it.
I'm going to say it again and again.
I'm pretty much the only one who doesn't like it, and I'm not even sure I like it.
It's a short cut.
You like it?
I don't like it much.
Describe it with your face.
It's hard.
Let's do it all at once.
That's fine.
Can I use my hands, too?
Sure.
It's just a little bit of face.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's go with the form.
Okay.
That one? That one?
Oh, that's it.Oh, this one.
Wait, wait, wait. They're all different.
That one? Which one?
When did you eat that?
Last time.
This is the last one I remember.
It smells so good.
Ginger, already.
Oh, I like it!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha!
I want some bread!
You smell like ginger.
I've already...
I've already decided.
Okay.
I couldn't do it after the first word.
Of course it didn't work.
What was it?
Peppers.
Aww!
I love it!
You love it.
I used to do a little bit of that.
I love it!
You said you loved it.
We were...
Celery.
Celery.Celery.
I made you choose parsley.
Hey.
Hey, that's not right.
Hey, it's not even close.
It's a game like this.
Okay!
Hot water's ready!
Yay!
Thank you!
Okay, guys.
First of all...
Here you go.
In position.
Thank you.
Wow, it smells so good!
I'm hungry.
Mom made this.
Let's eat first.
Yeah, I'm a little hungry.
Then match it.
I did.
Bon appétit.
Wow!
Delicious!
Delicious.
There's fox in it.
I like the salt.
It's so good.Very tasty
Strong taste
I love these noodles so much!
Fresh juice
super easy
super soupy
warm and fluffy
I'd eat them to death.
Delicious
I don't want to eat it anyway.
Want some?
Which way do you want it?
I can eat it while you watch.
Okay, okay.
I'll try to do it at the same time.
Okay, here we go.
Smells delicious.
Yum!
It's a little salty.
Yes, it is.
Delicious.
Ei... after this...
Your face!
It's so rich!
I love strong flavors!
Did you see the theme?
Let's start the game with a small udon!
What do you think of this?
I don't like it.
Dislike itI don't like it.
Hmm.
Some people don't like it.
I do.
You seem light.
It looks so light.
Seems very light
There.
If it were a girl
It's not light
Hmm...
What's wrong with it?
The color?
Hmm.
I don't know.
I mean, for me, it's...
It's a little lame.
It's kind of lame.
It's kind of transparent.
Hmmm...
Night moon.
Yellow. Yellow?
Yeah, yellow.
The shiny spot. Oh, there's yellow, too.
Yeah. - Yeah.
What's your weakness?
I don't know.something
What do you mean, "imaginary window"?
Fantasy? Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
It's all about the spirits.
I'm thinking.
Uh... uh...
It's normal.
I mean, all that fantasy stuff.
Maybe it's the Grim Reaper?
Huh?
Hohohoho?
Oh, I see. So you're not good with people.
No, I'm not good with people.
But I'd be happy if they were here.
What? I want one! Aren't you afraid of them?
I want one.
I want it.
Actually, I'm more interested in the story of how it showed up.
Well, then, here it is. The answer to your question.
It showed up.
Ehhhh...
I like the bangs.
But they're the same.
It's the same.
What about you?
I said "ehh".
I said "ehhhh".
Yuzuke's mindset isn't the same as mine at this point.Mind just yielding in the first place isn't the same thing as doing it now.
It's a little different.
It's hard to say.
So it's just a different mindset to begin with?
So that's a possibility.
I wonder if they'll be a little more aggressive.
Oh, I saw that.
You saw it.
I saw it.
Then you're out.
Yes, I understand.
What?
Do that thing...
Pose like that.
Okay.
Ready?
Oh!
What's that?
We're in this together.
We're the same.
That's it.
That's not it!
That's it!
Exciting Soul
Nagaya
Team Shan
OmoroInteresting.
Wow, they look so much alike, koharuna.
I'm lost
So, like pointing and pointing?
Yeah, I'm lost.
Okay.
Which one?
Yuzuki.
Nao?
Ehh...
The correct answer is... write your name?
Okay?
I'll name the decimalist.
The decimalist is... yujiki!
Yay!
I don't like it.
Fairies?
Yes, I do.
That's right.
The decimals were fairies and the decimals were ghosts.
I'll tell you what... we're on our way, and I've never heard of anyone being afraid of fairies before, so...
Go with him.
I said I didn't want to.
I don't like fairies.
I'm so disappointed.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Scary, scary, scary...
Haru wins the war. Yuzuki wins.
Yuzuki won.Yuzuki wins.
Yuzuki wins!
Yeah!
It's a game of "Yuzuki wins.
If you don't notice, you can't match.
I hear that a lot. It's fun.
I just changed the subject category to "Kid's Games.
Is it okay if it's for kids?
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's getting really warm in here. Is it ginger?
Is it ginger? It's so warm.
Let the games begin.
What's your feeling? I'm trying to get a feeling for this subject with you guys.
Emotions? I'm like, "Thank you.
Me too. Thank you for everything.
I'd be in a lot of trouble if I didn't. In a lot of trouble?
I guess I'm more in touch than most.
I think I'm more in touch than most.
You're right, it's annoying.
You're all still grateful?
Yeah, I'm very grateful.
I am.
I'll give you something of equal value.
Uh, gratitude level.
Gratitude level.
I'm pretty grateful.
Yeah, really.
Here you go.
Here you go. cop (police officer)
Wow.
That's certainly gratifying.
Oh, yeah.
I'm just a little more grateful.
Sanitizer.
Wet wipes.
Oh.
Here you go.
Sponge for the dishes.
You're gonna need it, right?
You did a great job.
How do you thank me for marrying you?
Marriage gratitude?
For four years of love?
At least a watch.
A watch?
That's a concept.
You mean time.
To each his own.
That's true.
But I guess Ho-chan uses it a lot.
I wonder if you use it.
That's true.
Do you have it?
Yes, I have it.
Definitely.
Do you carry it around?
Not so much.
What color?What color?
Basic
Basic color?
Basic color
Ochre.
Is that it?
Come on, white.
Brown?
Maybe some brown.
Oh, white? That's pretty high-end stuff.
You're using some pretty decent colors.
Well, I mean, it's kind of highbrow, but...
They looked white to me.
Oh, brown?
On the contrary, I like it.
When did you see Esaki?
Esaki?
Yesterday?
Where did you see him yesterday?
At home.
Which one?
I opened the door.
There he is.
I opened it.
Oh, my God.
I look bad white to everyone.
Am I crazy?
Wait a minute.
What did you open?What did you open?
I can't open it.
The shelf? I opened the cabinet, and there you are.
Yesterday? In the house? Do you see him every day?
No, I don't know. What are you talking about?
What is it? Maybe I'm, uh, part of a genus, you know, that's how you put it down.
Well, how do you use it?
I use it a lot.
Where do you put them? How do you use it? Try to use it in the simplest way, like that.
Well, the right answer is always the winner, right? Yeah, that's right.
How do you use it?
But that's it. Let me see.
There are many ways to use it. You need something like this.
Oh, like this? Some people use it like this?
Yes, yes. Some people don't. But it hurts.
It's definitely not good for the skin.
But it's good for the skin. Yeah.
I see it sometimes. Like where we eat.
I don't mind if you do it. I don't mind.
Yeah, I mean, I feel like it's pretty bad for the skin.
It's not good for the skin.
Are you hurt or something?
I'm gonna have to finger you.
Okay.
Don't point at your hand like that.
What's with that face?
I'm pretty sure that's Izuki.
It's not Izuki?
I'm so disappointed.
I was just thinking, you know, you say that like it's a resemblance.I thought, "You know, we're super similar.
Hey, I thought...
It's so frustrating.
Wow.
That's funny.
Definitely Osu.
I thought you were a big group guy.
Osu.
That's easy to understand.
Thank you for watching.
What was the topic at that time?
What did we all say?
Yuzuki used a toothpick.
Yuzuki squeezed the rice with a toothpick, right?
We finished it!
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Delicious, delicious, delicious!
It's so good!
It was delicious!
You did Kaori!
I'm going with Kaori.
We'll be together.
We'll see, won't we?
When you see it again with your friends...
Oh, it looks so good!
Please go there on your way home!
That's what I'm talking about
If you think it looks good and you liked it
Good button and comment!Good Buttons and Comments
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you!
That's all for now.
Bye bye.
[ED